# **Ana Bollain**

## Front-end Developer





### About me

Curious by nature, I define myself as persevering and resourceful. With great adaptability, my empathy, collaborative attitude and commitment make me a great team player.

Thanks to over 6 years of work experience in France and Spain, communicating in both English and French, I have mastered both project planning and stress management to meet client expectations with tight deadlines.

## Soft skills

Teamwork **Empathy** Problem Solving Attention to detail Creative Thinking Responsiveness Adaptability Management

## **Proyectos**

Rick & Morty 👄 Personal Project | React JS

Minion's Cards 👄 Team Project | Javascript

Breaking Bad C Personal Project | React JS

Legacy JS Code Upgrading 👄 Team Project | React & Node JS

Adalabers 👄 Personal Project | React JS

Whack Tartalo Personal Project | Javascript

Adatravellers (=) Team Project | HTML5 & CSS3

## **Experience**

#### Front-end Developer

Bootcamp Adalab | Remote | Sept. 2022 - Dec. 2022

- > Layout: HTML5, CSS3, Sass, Responsive Design, Flexbox, CSS Grid.
- > Javascript (ES6) and creation of a SPA with React.
- > Developing a basic REST API with Node JS and Express JS.
- > SQLite for creating and managing databases.
- > Version control with Git.
- > Project development under SCRUM framework and Agile philosophy.
- > Development tools: Gulp, Visual Studio Code, Terminal, Zeplin.
- > Communication skills and team work: Slack, Github, Railway.

#### Partner Architect & Freelance Interior Designer

Freelance. Remote | March 2022 - Oct. 2022 Estudi Biga SCCLP. Barcelona | Sept. 2019 - March 2022 Katty Schiebeck. Barcelona | April 2019 - Oct. 2019

- > Management and development of projects as a team leader.
- > Coordination of all parties involved in project decision-making.
- > Design, illustration and 3D rendering of creative proposals.
- > Production of technical and administrative documentation.
- > Adaptability to tight deadlines with high quality standards.

#### **Architect & Interior Designer**

Atelier du Pont. Paris | Jan. 2017 - March 2019 AWP. París | March 2016 - Oct. 2016

- > Contact with clients in oral presentations and project follow-up.
- > Analysis of commercial proposals and compliance with client's budget.
- > Contact with sales representatives for the prescription of materials.
- > Management and development of residential and hospitality projects.

## Education

### **Intensive Front-end Development Bootcamp**

Adalab | Remote | Sept. 2022 - Dec. 2022

#### Online Web Development Courses

Platzi | Remote | July 2022 - Sept. 2022 HTML5 & CSS3 | CSS Grid | Javascript | JS Engine (V8) & Browser

#### **Basics of Web Development & Coding**

Coursera. University of Michigan | Remote | April 2022 - June 2022

#### **Master of Architecture**

**Technical Skills** 

SQLite

ETSAM. Polytechnic University of Madrid | Sept. 2008 - July 2015

#### **Architecture & Landscape Exchange Program**

KTH. Sweden | Erasmus | Sept. 2012 - July 2013

#### Languages Spanish Native Git English Sass Professional, C1 Advanced (CAE) French Fluent

**Basque** 

Native, EGA